Shehzad Ahmed

Software Engineer | MERN Stack Developer

Karachi

shaxad.here@gmail.com

+92 303 2804856

Software Engineer currently working at Koderlabs, working on applications built on complex architectures, and different javascript-based technologies. In my spare time, I assist startups in product development and work on my own product ideas, I specialize in MERN Stack, but also have proficient skills in PHP and MySQL.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Work Experience

MERN Stack Developer

Koderlabs - Karachi November 2022 to Present

- Develop contemporary, high-performing, and easily maintainable code for a broad range of client and internal initiatives.
- Utilize various programming languages, platforms, frameworks, and content management systems like TypeScript, React.js, React Native, Vue.js and JavaScript.
- Interact with cross-functional teams of producers, designers, clients, and engineers daily.

MERN Stack Developer

Fine Solutions - Karachi February 2022 to October 2022

- Worked with a team of three designers to build a marketing website & auditing web application for UrAudits
- Interfaced with clients every week, providing technological expertise
- Worked on Next.js websites and landing pages.
- Worked on a Human Resource Management System.

MERN Stack Developer

ARTT - Karachi

November 2020 to January 2022

Worked on Learning Management Systems, Point of sale software, AWS S3, Student Data Management Systems, WebApps like Search Engine.

ASP.Net Developer

MarsoTech - Karachi March 2019 to April 2020

• Collaborated with a team of designers and developers to create a surveys web application using the ASP.NET MVC framework.

Education

HDSE I APTECH in Computer Software

Aptech Computer Education - Karachi June 2017 to May 2018

Skills

- React (2 years)
- Node.js (2 years)
- Javascript (3 years)
- PHP (3 years)

Languages

- English Expert
- Urdu Fluent

Links

https://github.com/Shaxadhere

https://shehzadahmed.tech

https://www.linkedin.com/in/shaxadhere/

Certifications and Licenses

Winner of TechOn Mobile App Development Competetion by Aptech

July 2021 to Present

Winner of TechOn in Webapplication Development by Aptech

September 2019 to Present

Winner of Ecompetencia-2019 in Web Application Development by Iqra University Karachi

April 2019 to Present

International Challenge on Informatics and Computational Thinking by Bebras International

September 2016 to Present